Now you've seen an example of an image broken down
你已经看过了一个例子 我们把一副图像
into a 2D grid of grayscale pixel values,
分解为灰阶像素值的 2D 网格
that has a width and a height.
包括宽度和高度值
But color images are a little different.
但彩色图像有点不同
Color images are interpreted as 3D cubes of values with width, height, and depth.
彩色图像可以表示为值的 3D 立方体 包括宽度、高度和深度
The depth is the number of color channels.
深度是颜色通道的数量
Most color images can be represented by combinations of only three colors: red,
大多数彩色图像都可以表示为三种颜色的组合：红
green, and blue values.
绿、蓝
These are known as RGB images and for RGB images,
它们被称为 RGB 图像 对于这些图像
the depth is three.
深度为 3
It's helpful to think of the depth as three stacked 2D color layers.
我们可以把深度想象为堆积在一起的 3 个 2D 颜色层
One layer is red,
一层是红色
one green, and one blue.
一层是绿色 一层是蓝色
And when stacked together,
堆积在一起时
they create a complete color image.
它们组成了一个完整的彩色图像
Now color images contain more information than grayscale images.
彩色图像比灰阶图像包括的信息更多
And they can add unnecessary complexity and take up more space in memory.
它们会增加不必要的复杂性 并且占用更多的内存空间
However, color images are also really useful for certain classification tasks.
但是 彩色图像对于某些分类任务非常有用
For example, say you want to classify lane lines in this image of a road.
例如 假设你想对这幅道路图像中的车道线进行分类
One of these lines is yellow and one is white.
其中一条线是黄色的 另一条是白色的
But which is which? You might see
但哪条是哪条呢 你可能看到
a slight difference in the grayscale intensity of the lane lines.
这些车道线的灰阶密度稍有不同
But the difference is so small and it varies under different lighting conditions.
但差别很小 在不同照明条件下还会变化
So, this grayscale image does not provide
因此 这幅灰阶图像并没有提供
enough information to distinguish between the yellow and white lane lines.
足够的信息 我们无法区分黄色和白色车道线
Let's see the color image for comparison.
我们看看彩色图像 对比一下
Here we can clearly see the difference between the white and yellow lane lines.
这里 我们能清楚看到 白色和黄色车道线的区别
And so we can tell a machine to recognize this difference too.
因此 我们也可以告诉机器 如何识别这种区别
So because this identification task is dependent on color,
因为该识别任务是依赖于颜色的
it's important that we work with color images.
因此 我们必须使用彩色图像
In general, when you think of a computer vision application like identifying lane lines,
一般来说 当考虑计算机视觉应用时 比如识别车道线
or cars or people.
车辆或行人时
You can decide whether color information and color images are useful,
你可以通过和自己的视觉类比 判断出色彩信息
by thinking about your own vision.
和彩色图像是否有用
If the identification problem is easier in color for us humans,
如果使用彩色识别对人类更简单
it's likely easier for an algorithm to see color images too.
那让算法来观察彩色图像也会更简单